something i've seen a lot today where people are like ice now is shooting people and this is their
10th shooting in the last year in chicago there's been two a woman who was shot five times
and they tried to same thing say that she was um rammed her vehicle into them
they tried to file charges against her the judge gets all the evidence and he's texting his fucking
ice buddies saying shot her five times but she had seven bullets put that in your book boys
another man had been living here for 20 years they on his way to work and they shot him through his car
window too and they also again tried to say that he tried to ram them they did this in la they just
did this too in um baltimore they just did this in baltimore too they've been doing this guys
what happened when people finally saw george floyd the video footage of george floyd heard
the recording of elijah mcclain what happened when we saw sonia massey that's why we record
and that's why we don't ever believe we we don't act as stenographers for the police and ice i never
report what they say i wait until i hear the other side where i stick to the absolute facts
there's no both sides when one side carries weapons with impunity